Previously, on Friends...
How did the
job stuff go?
He offered me one.
You know what? This calls for
a bottle of Israel's finest.
The job is in Paris.
Oh God, please,
somebody say something.
So, if you take this job,
you'll be...
you'll be moving to Paris?
Or facing a bitch of a commute.
I know,
I know...
It's huge, and it's scary
and it's really far, far away
from you guys.
But this is such an incredible
opportunity for me.
And I've already talked
to them
about our situation
with Emma.
And they said they'll do
whatever we need
to make us feel comfortable.
Okay.
I mean, I'll fly
back and forth.
They'll fly you out,
anything we want.
My boss said I might be getting
a new lamp in my cubicle.
All right.
We'll work it out.
Oh, thank you!
Thank you!
Yeah.
Oh!
You sure this
is what you want?
I think it is.
( chuckles )
Ooh, what's going on?
I got a really incredible
job offer.
Hey, great!
Good for you!
All right!
It's in Paris.
What?! No! No! No!
No! No! No! No! No! No!
Too much is changing, okay?
First Phoebe getting married!
Congratulations.
And then... and then these two
moving to a stupid house
in the stupid suburbs!
Hey! This afternoon,
you said you'd be supportive.
Well, it comes and goes!
I wouldn't trust it!
Well, you guys, this is really,
really important to me,
and it means a lot
if you can try to get on board.
Of course we can.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Yay!
Oh!
Joey?
No, no, no!
No, no.
My hugs are reserved for people
staying in America!
Joey, it would mean...
Hey, no, hey, get your
France-going arms away from me!
Are you okay with this?
Well, it makes me
feel sad, but...
Talking to Ross.
I see.
Well, Rachel moving
to another country?
Not being able to see her
every day?
How could I be okay with this?
I know, but what are we
gonna do?
She really needs this job.
Do you think if, uh...
if the Ralph Lauren people
offered her her old job back,
she would take it?
Well, how is that
going to happen?
Is this the best way
to use one of your
three magic wishes?
Like, I don't know.
I could talk to her boss.
Yeah!
I met him
at that Christmas party.
I mean, we really hit it off.
You mean, the guy
who kept calling you "Ron"?
I didn't say we were brothers!
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey, Phoebe?
Hi!
Hey, um, tell me
what you think.
All right, the house
next door to the one
that we're buying in Westchester
just went on the market.
Now, I want to take a look
at it, but Chandler doesn't.
We close escrow tomorrow,
so seeing another house
can only confuse us.
And we're easily confused.
We're not very bright.
But what if it's better
than ours?
Shouldn't we at least look?
What do you
think, Pheebs?
Well, I think that shirt
makes you look
like you should work
at a Baskin-Robbins.
Anyway...
Hey, isn't Joey's agent
Estelle Leonard?
Yeah.
She died.
You're kidding.
That's terrible.
Yeah, last Saturday.
Wow! She was the first black man
to fly solo across the Atlantic!
Oh, wait a minute.
I read the wrong one.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, she was just an agent.
Joey's going to be
so upset.
I know. He always wanted
to be the first black man
to cross the Atlantic.
Well, we cannot tell Joey
about this.
He's already flipping out about
everything that's changing.
This'll push him over the edge.
Seriously, you don't think
we should tell him?
Well, not for a little while.
Let's just give him a few days
to get used to everything else.
Well, what if he reads it
in the paper?
Unless Snoopy says it
to Charlie Brown, I
think we're okay.
May I help you?
Yeah. I'm a friend
of Rachel Green's.
Um, actually, we-we met
at the Christmas party
about two years ago.
Oh, right. Uh, Don?
Close. Ron.
Well, uh...
what can I do for you?
Um, well, I'm here to see
if-if, uh, you'll give
Rachel her job back.
Ah, did she ask you
to come here and do this?
Oh, no. First, I have
to get you to agree.
Then we'll see
if she wants to come back.
Wow. That is tempting.
Look, she loved her job here.
And let's face it,
you're not going to find anyone
who did it as well as she did.
Isn't that true?
She is good.
Huh. I took a shot there.
But I'm sorry,
there's nothing I can do.
Well, that's not true.
There's nothing I want to do.
I see.
Thanks very much.
Mm-hmm.
Is this your son?
Yeah.
His name is Ross.
What?
Uh, nothing.
It's just... it's, uh...
it's close to "Ron".
Does he, um...
does little Ross like dinosaurs,
by any chance?
Yeah, they're all
he talks about. Why?
How would he like to come
with me
to the Museum
of Natural History,
after everyone else has left--
just the two of us--
and he can touch
anything he wants?
I just heard it
how you must have heard it,
and that's not good.
Um, let me start again.
I'm a paleontologist.
Uh, you'll be
there with us.
And the touching refers
only to bones-- fossils!
You could really
arrange that?
You let Rachel come back,
and it's done.
Well...
I guess having Rachel back
wouldn't be the worst thing
in the world.
Yes! Oh, thank you!
This is great.
Thank you so much.
And I swear, your kid's going
to have the time of his life.
That's great.
I worry about little Ross.
He's always reading,
he's collecting rocks,
and he's obsessed
with dinosaurs.
He'll be fine!
Hey, Pheebs.
Hey.
Everything okay?
I'm just mad at my agent.
Estelle? Why?
Well, there's a part
in this TV movie
that I would be perfect for,
and I didn't even
get put up for it.
She better have
a good reason.
I'm guessing she does.
Yeah, well... I wanna
hear it, because she
keeps doing this.
Well, no, wait, wait, wait!
I... all right,
I-I got to go.
Just listen.
Promise me
that you will wait a minute
before you call her.
Oh, okay. Why?
Because a promise
between friends
means never having
to give a reason.
I love that saying!
( muttering )
( cell phone rings )
Hello?
( in gruff voice ):
Joey, it's Estelle.
I was just gonna call you.
That's weird.
It's a little coincidental,
but believable.
Listen,
I'm sure you're wondering
why I didn't get you
an audition for that TV movie.
Yeah, actually, I am.
I guess I dropped
the ball there.
Whoopsy!
That's it?!
You know, it seems like all
you do lately is drop the ball.
Don't take that tone with me.
Who do you think you are?
Alan Lemon, the first black man
to fly solo across the Atlantic?
No-No. Look, all I'm saying is,
you're my agent, okay?
And you're not getting me
into any auditions,
and I'm tired of it!
What are you saying?
I'm saying that...
this isn't working
for me anymore.
Okay, Estelle?
You're fired. Good-bye.
Man!
Tough week for Estelle.
Hi.
Emma left her stuffed T-rex
at my house.
You know she can't
sleep without it.
Ah, well, she's asleep now.
Stop forcing that thing on her.
Okay.
Oh! You're not
gonna believe
what happened
to me today!
Ralph Lauren called
and gave me my job back.
No!
Yeah!
I mean,
it was the weirdest thing.
They fire me,
and then out of nowhere,
they just hire me back.
I mean, that place must just be
falling apart without me.
So, you're not
going to Paris?
No, I'm still going!
What?!
Ooh!
( chuckling )
What?!
Well, when the Louis Vuitton
people found out
that Ralph Lauren
wanted me back,
they offered me more money.
Isn't that great?!
Yay!
Whoo!
( knocking at door )
Hi. We're buying
the house next door,
and we were wondering if we
could just take a look around.
Oh, sure! I'm showing it
to someone else right now,
but please, look around.
Thanks.
I feel like we're cheating
on our house.
And if we're gonna cheat,
shouldn't it be with, like,
a hot, younger house that does
stuff that our house won't do?
Wow!
Ours is so much better.
This living room
is smaller.
The dining room
looks like a cave.
What a hole!
So... what do you think?
Love it! Yeah.
Well, we already have
one offer on it,
and I think the lady upstairs
is going to make another one.
They could be our neighbors.
What are they like?
Oh, the woman upstairs
is very nice.
She and her husband
have two kids.
Uh he's on Wall Street,
and she's...
Oh... my... God!
Sure.
( knocking on door )
Hey, Joey, you want
to come with me to...
Are you okay?
Yeah, I just...
I just feel bad
about firing Estelle.
This has got to be killing her.
( clears throat )
No. That wouldn't kill her.
A coronary embolism might.
I don't know.
She's got to be taking it hard.
I was, like,
her only client.
Mm-hmm.
Except for this guy
who eats paper.
And I'm guessing he eats
more money than he makes.
Look, I know
she's not a great agent,
but she did stick with me
for ten years.
I'm gonna call her
and hire her again.
No, no, no!
Don't-Don't call her.
You wait for her to call you.
Why?
Because patience is the road
to understanding...
which is the key
to a happy heart.
You blow me away.
All, right, so promise
you're going to wait
for her to call you?
I promise.
Okay.
And that means...
never having to give a reason.
What a small world.
And yet I never run
into Beyonce.
You two know each other?
Oh, we go way back.
Before Monica made
an honest man out of him,
Chandler used to be
my little love muffin.
( braying laughter )
So, are you guys thinking
of getting this house, too?
Ooh, are we going to have
a bidding war?
I better warn you,
I'm a toughie.
( braying laughter)
Don't... Don't...
Don't!
No, actually,
we're buying the
house next door.
( delighted gasp )
Why?
I don't know why.
Ooh, that decides it then.
I was on the fence,
but knowing that you two
would be our neighbors...
( shrieks )...
now we have to get it!
Ellen,
we're going to talk numbers.
( braying chuckle )
This cannot be happening.
Okay, the Realtor said
another couple
made an offer.
Maybe the Janices won't get it.
Maybe the other
couple will.
The only way that that is going
to happen is
if the other couple are
the Hitlers.
Okay, okay.
All right, what if we get
both houses?
Huh? We can turn this house
into a guest house.
That's a great idea.
And, by the way, and I don't
mean to be distasteful,
but when did you
start crapping money?
Okay, you come up with an idea.
All right,
all right, all right.
We've still got three hours
until escrow closes
on our house.
We can still get out.
But we love our house.
Will we love it so much
with her next door?
And she's going to be
louder out here, too.
Just the crickets and
"Oh... my... God!"
Okay. But if we don't get
this house,
she's still going to show up
wherever we go.
I mean, at least if she's here,
it eliminates the element
of surprise.
I mean, never again will you
have to hear the three words
that make your balls jump
back up inside your body.
Well, we have to do something.
We can't have her living
next door.
( braying laughter )
Ah, that does it, too.
( knocking on door )
Who is it?
It's me... Ron.
( sighs )
Look, I, uh, I know
Rachel turned you down,
but I think there's a way
you might be able
to get her to come back.
This may surprise you,
but rehiring fired employees
is not my main job.
Well...
Just hear me out.
How would you feel
about offering her a raise?
Not good, Ron.
Perhaps I can
persuade you.
What if you could
give your son this...
genuine pterodactyl egg replica?
Wow. That's, uh,
that's pretty cool.
Yeah? So... do we have a deal?
Okay, you got it.
Yes! Yes.
This is going to make me
very popular.
Oh... ( chuckles )
Believe me, the ladies,
they love it.
I meant with my son.
Good, 'cause the ladies,
not so much.
MAN ( on machine ):
Joey, this is Al Zeebooker,
the guy who eats paper.
I'm sure you've heard
that Estelle passed away.
I wanted to let you know
there's a memorial for her,
at the Westside Chapel,
tomorrow at 10:00.
Hope you can make it.
Oh, my God.
( phone rings )
( beeps )
Hello.
( Estelle's voice ):
Joey, it's Estelle.
Estelle?
Yeah.
I wanted to call and tell you
that there's no hard feelings
for firing me.
Okay.
I just, I can't believe
you're calling me.
Well, I didn't think
I should just drop by.
No, no! Don't drop by!
Don't drop by!
Don't, don't, no, no...
Anyway,
you did what you had to do.
I'm okay.
Uh, c-can I ask you something?
Um...
What's it like there?
It's all right.
Look, kiddo,
I got to go.
Good luck with the career.
You're gonna be huge.
Thanks for everything, Estelle.
Bye.
( beeps )
"Out of area."
Boy, I'll say!
Well...
I just talked to Sid.
We are definitely putting
in an offer on the house.
And I'll bet we get it!
The Hitlers will be
so disappointed.
All right, I-I got to run.
Tell Monica I say good-bye.
And... I'll see you later.
Neighbor...
( braying laughter )
Wait!
I just want you to know that...
I'm so happy
you're going to be here.
Oh! Me too!
( laughs )
Because!
That way... we can pick up
where we left off.
Huh?
I never stopped loving you.
Oh... my...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want you... I need you.
I must have you, Janice
Litman-Goralnik nee Hosenstein.
Chandler, what are
you talking about?
Now that you live next door,
we can be together every day.
Sid and Monica
never have to know a thing.
I don't know
what to say.
I mean, you know,
obviously...
we have this...
heat between us.
Obviously.
But I love my husband.
And I know you love your wife.
I-I don't think
we should get this house now
Don't say that. Don't dangle
the dream, then take it away.
Chandler,
one of us has
got to be strong.
I understand.
Although...
maybe just...
one last moment of weakness.
( grunts )
( sighs )
Good-bye, Chandler Bing.
( strained ):
They're never coming down now.
( knocking )
Hi.
You are never
going to believe
what happened
to me today.
What?
Ralph Lauren called,
again, and they offered me
more money.
They did?!
Yes.
It was the weirdest thing.
Zelner called me
and he said,
"We will do anything
we can to get you back,"
and that I should thank
some Ron.
I don't even know what
department that guy's in.
( stammers )
So, what are you,
what are you going to do?
Well, I took it.
That's great.
So you're staying in New York.
( both cheering )
Yay... uh...
You're-You're
excited, right?
Yeah... Yeah.
The money's great.
It's certainly
the easier choice.
Right.
But you know, was I looking
forward to going to Paris? Sure.
You know, was I excited
about working
in the fashion capital
of the world?
Oh, absolutely!
( sighs )
Yeah, but, you know, this is...
it's fine.
I'm fine going back to a job
where I've pretty much gotten
everything out of it
that I possibly can.
( sighs )
Um... I had no...
I had no idea you were,
you were so excited about Paris.
Um, I mean,
you said you were scared.
Well, yeah, I mean, it was
good-scared, though, you know.
Like when
I-moved-to-New-York scared.
Or, uh, when I-found-out-
I-was-going-to-have-Emma scared.
But this is... fine.
This is going to be good.
You should go.
What?
It's what you want;
you should go.
Do you really think so?
I really do.
But I already told Zelner
that I would come back.
I'm sure he'll understand.
All right.
All right. I'm going to do it.
I'm going to go to Paris.
Yeah.
Yeah!
I'm going to Paris!
Thank you, Ross.
Yeah, yeah.
Aw.
Oh, I'm so happy.
( sighs )
Then I'm happy, too.
Aw.
Thank you all for coming.
We're here today to pay our
respects to a wonderful agent
and a beautiful woman.
Inside.
As Estelle's only two clients,
we would like
to say a few words.
Dude, where's my speech?
( gulps )
That is entertaining.
Al Zeebooker, everybody!
( scattered applause )
Yeah.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org